http://www.leevalleylions.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Who we are
Our website address is: //www.leevalleylions.co.uk.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: //automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
If you contact us the information you supply is used solely to reply to you and is then deleted.  If you submit your details because you are interested in playing for the Lions then the information you provide will be forwarded to the team’s coach/manager and again, it will be used to contact you in this respect and for no other purpose.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (eg videos, images, articles, etc). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Who we share your data with
We do not share your data with anyone.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
UPCOMING GAMESNo games for nowTWITTERRetweet on TwitterLee Valley Lions RetweetedLee Valley Ice@LeeValleyIce·1 DecFollowing the Govt announcement, we’re delighted to be reopening on Thursday 3 December.
We’re in a Tier 2 COVID area and operate a COVID secure site. For more information on our safety measures and what’s available to book click here: //ow.ly/Nc4A50CznwmReply on Twitter 1333784117176119296Retweet on Twitter 13337841171761192962Like on Twitter 13337841171761192963Twitter 1333784117176119296Retweet on TwitterLee Valley Lions RetweetedLee Valley Ice@LeeValleyIce·7 OctDelighted that Waltham Forest Council have given approval in principle to our plans for a new ice centre!
A big thank you to everyone who contributed to the plans.
We are proud to be able continue serving the community.
You can learn more at //icecentreredevelopment.com/ Reply on Twitter 1313826177967108096Retweet on Twitter 13138261779671080968Like on Twitter 131382617796710809632Twitter 1313826177967108096Retweet on TwitterLee Valley Lions RetweetedJacob Ranson@JacobRanson27·9 OctOlympic ice rink venue in East London passes first planning hurdle @LeeValleyPark @LeeValleyLions
//www.eastlondonadvertiser.co.uk/sport/football/olympic-ice-rink-venue-in-east-london-passes-first-planning-hurdle-1-6877030Reply on Twitter 1314572448441004033Retweet on Twitter 13145724484410040337Like on Twitter 131457244844100403335Twitter 1314572448441004033Load More...JUNIOR LIONS Find out about the junior Lee Valley Lions at www.leevalleylions.org.uk
